

# ARRASYID FADEL FATONSYAH

## **Fullstack Developer**

Kudus, Central Java

- aff.anton20@gmail.com
- 089-635-164-141
- <u>@arrasyidff-github</u>
- <u>arrasyid-fadel-fatonsyah-</u> <u>linkedin</u>
- arfafa-web

#### **ABOUT ME**

My name is Arrasyid Fadel Fatonsyah, I'm 25 years old. I'm a Backend Developer, but I'm also interested in the Frontend side. For most of my projects, I am responsible for the backend side. I am also always enthusiastic about new things with what I do, and I can contribute well as a team and individually.

VUE

CSSSCSS

REACT

JOUERY

TAILWIND

#### **SKILLS**

- JAVASCRIPT
- NODE.JS
- EXPRESS.JS
- SEQUELIZE
- OLQOLLILL
- PHP
- LARAVEL
- MYSQL
- POSTGRESQL
- MONGODB
- RESTFULL API

#### **PORTFOLIO**

#### Web Portfolio

### https://667a37704eadfa828a0cc350-arfafa.netlify.app/

This website is designed to provide a comprehensive overview of my background, skills, experience, and projects I have worked on. The main purpose of this website is to make it easier for you to find out more about me and my work through an attractive and informative display

#### School Static Web

https://school-mb.web.app/

Create a static website with a school theme and add information from the school

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **BACKEND DEVELOPER**

PT. INOSOFT TRANS SISTEM

November 2021 - Now

Add, change, and fix features as requested. And also help the team to solve existing problems so that the web application can work according to its function

#### **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

CV. AKASA TECH DWIJAYA BALI

April 2021 - Nov 2021

Add, change, and fix features as requested. And also help the team to solve existing problems so that the web application can work according to its function

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **HACKTIV8 INDONESIA**

FULLSTACK IMMERSIVE / FULLSTACK JAVASCRIPT 9/2021 - 1/2022

Learn new things and complete assignments every day with tight deadlines. Also, create several projects with the things learned previously

#### ITB STIKOM BALI

SISTEM INFORMASI

08/2018 - 09/2020 (Unfinished - 4th Semester)
Decided not to continue studying during Covid. And decided to continue learning at the Hacktiv8
Indonesia Bootcamp, so I can start working straight away